Kelli Uyeda

kelli@uyeda.me | (626) 641-2379 | South Pasadena, CA https://uyeda.me | linkedin.com/in/kelli-uyeda | github.com/kellikells

Full-Stack Web Developer

College graduate with a bachelor's degree in English, and primarily self-taught developer driven by curiosity. Achieved Full Stack Development Certification and has been helping businesses improve or create applications as necessary. Leveraging a background in hospitality to coalesce and build a more intuitive user experience on the web. Known for abilities to problem solve, meet deadlines, and be a successful team player.

Team-Based Projects:

Iphy Weather: Primary focused on back-end development to create a web application that provides the user with weather information based on location. Added user's ability to search weather conditions by *zipcode* or *city&state*. Successfully completed the project working with a team of 4 members in 12 days.

Five Star Foodies: Implemented MVC design pattern to build a restaurant search engine utilizing YelpAPI. Worked with another team member to incorporate secure user authentication with Auth0 alongside React and Node.js.

Education

University of California Los Angeles Extension – Full Stack Developer Certification
University of California Los Angeles - Bachelor of Arts in English

Technology Summary

ES6 JavaScript | TypeScript | React | JSX | jQuery | HTML5 | CSS | Tailwind CSS

Python | Java | Node.is

Express.js | Django | Flask

AWS | Vercel | Heroku | Git

SQL | MongoDB | Contentful | Firebase

Windows | Mac

Work Experience

Full Stack Developer Los Angeles, CA 2019-Present

Dan Pasadena, CA 2018-2019

Gyu Kaku Pasadena, CA 2014-2018